# Ziady Mubaraq

Frontend Engineer, Instructor

Jakarta, Indonesia | 14 Dec 1996 | © (+62) 85186661414 | ⊠ ziady.mubaraq@gmail.com

Ø ziterz.dev | ♥ github.com/ziterz | to linkedin.com/in/ziterz

# Summary

Experienced Frontend Engineer specializing in Web and Mobile Development, with a track record of developing 10+ applications. Has 4 years of experience as a Full-Stack JavaScript Instructor, mentoring 800+ students in fundamentals and advanced topics. Achieved significant improvements in student scores with a 93% satisfaction rate.

# **Technical Skills**

- Web: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, Node.js, Vue.js, React.js, Next.js
- Mobile: React Native, Expo, Swift, UIKit, SwiftUI, CocoaPods
- Others: OOP, MVC/MVVM, RESTful APIs, Firebase, Git, Agile, Jira, TDD, Unit Testing

# **Professional Experience**

#### **HACKTIV8 INDONESIA - Part Time Instructor**

Apr 2024 - Present

• Teaching part time programs in Hacktiv8 and Prakerja classes for various courses such as web development, mobile development, and software analysis.

#### **APPLE DEVELOPER ACADEMY - iOS Developer (Intern)**

Feb - Dec 202

• Deepening expertise in iOS Development, design, and project management, including Apple Frameworks, Design Patterns, and HIG principles. Launched 5+ applications on TestFlight and the App Store.

# HACKTIV8 INDONESIA - Lead Phase Full-Stack JavaScript Instructor

Jan 2020 - Feb 2023

- Supervise a team of 6-8 colleagues responsible for evaluating and observing the learning process and instructors.
- Maintain curriculum progress, teach, guide, and regularly assess student progress.
- Teaching courses such as JavaScript, Node.js, Express.js, Vue.js, React.js, React Native, Redux, TDD, Jest, MongoDB, GraphQL, Docker and Microservices.

# **Related Projects**

# Riot Board Game - iOS Developer

Sep - Nov 2023

- Created a hybrid board game for 2-4 players with a native iOS that integrates NFC cards and digital elements.
- Using Xcode, SwiftUI, CoreNFC, and AVKit.

#### **HCIS Imeco - Front End Developer**

Sep 2022 - Jan 2023

• Built the HCIS (Human Capital Information System) application for a company, employee data, salaries, attendance, and company requirements using Vue 3, Pinia, Vite, Maps, and TailwindCSS.

# **Speed Online - Mobile Developer**

Feb - Apr 2022

• Built the Speed Online mobile application for ordering ship crossing tickets in North Kalimantan using Vue 3, Quasar, Vuex, Maps, WhatsApp OTP, and Xendit Payment Gateway.

#### Flona Store - Front End Developer

Nov 2021 - Jun 2022

• Developed the Flona Store Marketplace, a platform for selling houseplant collections from Indonesia and around the world, with international shipping, using Vue, Vuex, Maps, ApexCharts, and Bootstrap Vue.

# Jastipin Aja - Mobile Developer

Oct - Dec 2020

• Developed the Jastipin Aja mobile application for Aldeoz Group to offer same-day delivery of regional food during the pandemic era, using React, React Native, Paper, Firebase, OneSignal, and Midtrans Payment Gateway.

#### Dicicilaja - Lead Android Developer

Jan - Dec 2019

• Created the Dicicilaja app for Adira Finance, featuring marketplace and sales functionalities, with 100K+ downloads on the Play Store, using Android Studio, Java, Kotlin, RxJava, Firebase, and OneSignal.

# **Recent Certifications**

# App Development with Swift Certified User by Apple

Feb 2024

Certificate of Completion

#### **Apple Developer Academy Certificate**

**Dec 2023** 

Certificate of Completion

# Swift Student Challenge WWDC 2023 by Apple

May 2023

Swift Student Challenge Winner

# **Educational Background**

#### INDONESIA UNIVERSITY OF EDUCATION

Aug 2015 - Oct 2019